His eyes are flaming glow. Using his visual paralysis he won numerous battle and got numerous jutsu by his pocket. He had a great friend named 
Hashirama Senju who was a sweet heart and kind hearted guy who take along everybody and think about everybody as his family later on they both led
the Konoha(The village in Hidden leaves). Then later on madara found out that there is a world that can be created using the his visual jutsu
which contain no misery and everybody can live in a world with peace and no harm to each other. Then he walk down a path of great effort to create
that path into a reality. He even fought his own friends Hashirama and lost against him and later on the new decendent of his clan and Hashirama's
clan created the end of his deadly war against brother and created the long lived peace by there hardwork and dedication. There name was
Naruto Uzumaki and Sasuke Uchiha.
